https://foodbank.org/privacy-policy/

Skip navigation508-842-3663PARTNER AGENCY PORTAL
Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Privacy PolicyReviewed January 29, 2020Worcester County Food Bank strongly believes in protecting the integrity and privacy of personal information gathered from our supporters through all of our communication channels, as well as from visitors to our Website. The protection of your privacy is of great importance to us, so we have created this privacy policy to communicate our practices regarding the collection and dissemination of personal information that you provide to us and that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, postal address, telephone number(s), email address, or any other information, provided to us by our supporters and Website visitors (hereinafter “Personal Information”), as well as certain non-personally identifiable information collected when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g. Google Chrome or Firefox), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac), the domain name of your internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Charter, Comcast or Verizon), aggregate data about the number of visits to the Site and/or aggregate data about the pages visited (hereinafter “Aggregate Data”).This policy also applies when you use social media that overlaps Worcester County Food Bank’s social media and/or website. This policy does not apply to information or data Worcester County Food Bank purchases from other sources. Worcester County Food Bank uses its best efforts to not share information it collects from those persons it provides services to (commonly referred to as “clients”).This policy will be updated periodically, so please be sure to reread it from time to time. The most recent date the privacy policy was updated is provided at the top of the page. By submitting your personal information to us, you are agreeing that Worcester County Food Bank may use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.Worcester County Food Bank’s Collection and Use of Personal Information:Worcester County Food Bank collects Personal Information supplied to us voluntarily by supporters, volunteers, and visitors to this Website. We may use such voluntarily provided information to improve our understanding of your interests, to improve our services, or to contact you for future support. In order to utilize certain features of our site or receive information from Worcester County Food Bank or make a donation, you may choose to provide Personal Information. If you do submit information to us, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was submitted. We may also use your information in other ways, such as to contact you about other Worcester County Food Bank activities and/or fundraising campaigns, to conduct matching on Facebook or other social media, or as otherwise disclosed to you at the point of collection.  We may also use your name, postal address and telephone number(s) to contact you offline. If you do not wish us to contact you offline, receive such mailings or share your information with these organizations, you may opt out by contacting us at development@foodbank.org.Worcester County Food Bank uses third-party vendors to provide services on this Website and in offline business operations. The information that you submit on this site may be provided to those vendors on a confidential basis so that those vendors can provide services (such as maintaining our database, sending email messages, facilitating fundraising activities, or processing credit card transactions) on our behalf.Other than as described in this privacy policy, or as may be necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of our organization or others, or as may be necessary to comply with applicable law, Worcester County Food Bank will not give or sell the Personal Information you provide online.Worcester County Food Bank uses the non-personally identifiable Aggregate Data information to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable Worcester County Food Bank to personalize your Internet experience. Worcester County Food Bank may use the Aggregate Data to analyze Site usage as well as create services and/or products to fit your needs. Also, Worcester County Food Bank shares this Aggregate Data with Worcester County Food Bank’s related entities, advertisers, partners, and/or other third-party vendors. Worcester County Food Bank shall own such Aggregate Data and maintain copies of such as part of its records.Use of Email Address:When you donate to Worcester County Food Bank or sign up on our Website, take an advocacy action, share your story or complete some other data form, you will be asked to supply your email address and other Personal Information. Worcester County Food Bank does not sell or rent your email address to any third party. Worcester County Food Bank does share your email address with local food banks in the Worcester County Food Bank Network. Email addresses gathered from donors or subscribers to Worcester County Food Bank are only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, to member food banks, and to contracted service providers and vendors for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.Worcester County Food Bank and its network of member food banks will only use your email address to send information about Worcester County Food Bank and our network (such as news and events, special programs, and fundraising). From time to time, we may send out email messages that might include information about like-missioned organizations and companies, but we do not provide them with access to any personal information that you have provided.Worcester County Food Bank complies with those provisions of the CAN-SPAM Act applicable to charitable organizations. All email messages contain a link to unsubscribe from Worcester County Food Bank email. You may subscribe or unsubscribe to Worcester County Food Bank at any time by contacting Worcester County Food Bank, or sending a notice by United States mail to the address at the end of this policy. Worcester County Food Bank holds the Better Business Bureau’s Accredited Charity Seal and follows the Direct Marketing Association’s Guidelines for Ethical Business Practice.User Submissions:Worcester County Food Bank welcomes your comments and participation on its site. However, you acknowledge that if you send us creative suggestions, stories, photos, videos, ideas, notes, drawings, concepts, or other information, the information shall be deemed, and shall remain, the property of Worcester County Food Bank. By submission of any information to us, you assign to us and we shall exclusively own all now known or hereafter existing rights to such information and shall be entitled to unrestricted use of the information for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, without compensation.As a user of this site, you are responsible for your own communications and are responsible for the consequences of their posting. Therefore, do not impersonate another person and not transmit material to us that is copyrighted, unless you are the copyright owner of have the permission of the copyright owner to post it; do not send material that reveals trade secrets, unless you won them or have the permission of the owner; do not send material that infringes on any other intellectual property rights of others or on the privacy or publicity rights of others; do not send material that is obscene, defamatory, threatening, harassing, abusive, hateful, or embarrassing to another user or any other person or entity; and do not send sexually explicit images, advertising or solicitations of business, or chain letters.You represent and warrant that any information and/or material you post or provide to Worcester County Food Bank through any medium is truthful, accurate, not misleading, not confidential property of others, and not in violation of any other third party’s rights. Furthermore, you acknowledge and agree that all submissions will become the property of Worcester County Food Bank and that Worcester County Food Bank has the right to publish or republish the submission for any type of use including for promotional and advertising purposes without compensation to you of any kind. Should your submission include third party materials, you grant, represent and warrant that you, as well as the owner of such content, have expressly granted Worcester County Food Bank a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide exclusive license to use the submission in any manner, media or form now known or hereafter developed. Worcester County Food Bank shall have the right to sub-license its rights.Use of “Cookies”:The Worcester County Food Bank Website may use “cookies” and similar means to collect aggregate statistical information. Aggregate information does not identify any individual person. We may use or disclose aggregate information for any purpose. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and are designed to be read only by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies are also used to recognize visitor preferences, temporarily store session information and past activity at our site in order to provide better service and easier access when individuals return to our site. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Websites you visit.Disabling Cookies:To remove cookies from your computer, visit your Internet browser’s “Help” section for information on how to delete cookies. In addition, there are many Websites that provide browser and operating system specific information on how to delete cookies. When thinking about whether you want to delete cookies, you should be aware that some sites require cookies to function properly. After you delete cookies, you may have to re-register with some sites or you may notice difficulty in browsing some sites.Security:This Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. The security measures used on this site include, but are not limited to, the operation of secure data networks protected by industry standard firewalls and password protected systems and internal policies to maintain the security of stored data. While we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.WarrantiesWORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS OF ANY KIND CONCERNING THE ACCURACY, SUITABILITY, OR SAFETY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL SUCH INFORMATION IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITH SPECIFIC DISCLAIMER OF ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS OF ANY KIND THAT THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY THIS WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, ERROR-FREE, OR THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER THAT HOSTS THE SITE ARE FREE FROM VIRUSES OR OTHER FORMS OF HARMFUL COMPUTER CODE. IN NO EVENT SHALL WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK, ITS EMPLOYEES, AGENTS OR ANY OTHER PERSON WHO HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THIS WEBSITE, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES RESULTING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE OR ANY LINKED SITE.EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED, WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY, CONTENT, AVAILABILITY OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, SERVICES OR MERCHANDISE FOUND ON THIRD PARTY STIES THAT LINK TO OR FROM THE WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK SITE.  WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR PRODUCT OR SERVICE ORDERING FUNCTIONS, ORDER FULFILLMENT OR COMPLIANCE OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WITH ANY MANUFACTURER’S WARRANTIES OR SPECIFICATIONS.  WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK CANNOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR THE MATERIAL CONTAINED ON THIRD PARTY SITES AND/OR RELATED SERVICES NOR DOES WORCESTER COUNTY FOOD BANK MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION YOU MIGHT BE REQUESTED TO GIVE TO THIRD PARTY SITES.External LinksLinks to other Websites do not imply an endorsement of the materials disseminated at those Websites, nor does the existence of a link to another site imply that the organization or person publishing at that site endorses any of the materials at this site. Links to other Websites are provided by Worcester County Food Bank as a convenience to its users. Worcester County Food Bank is not responsible for the materials contained at any Website linked to this site. If you visit the Websites of any of our partners, please consult their privacy policy. Our privacy policies apply only to your use of the Worcester County Food Bank site and direct interactions with Worcester County Food Bank. We do not disclose personally identifiable information to those operating linked sites and we are not responsible for their privacy practices.A Special Note About Children:Worcester County Food Bank does not knowingly gather any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. You must be 13 years of age or older to access the site. Worcester County Food Bank has no interest in collecting information from children under the age of 13.Binding Effect/Modification of Policy and TermsBy accessing the Worcester County Food Bank Website, you agree that the terms, combined with your act of using the Website and/or services offered on or through the Website have the same legal force and effect as a written contract with your written signature and satisfy any laws that require a writing or signature, including any applicable stature of frauds. You further agree that you shall not challenge the validity, enforceability or admissibility of the terms on the grounds that it was electronically transmitted or authorized. In addition, you acknowledge that you have had the opportunity to print the terms.Worcester County Food Bank may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changed or amended Privacy Policy on the Website. Your continued viewing of or use of this Website following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to any such changes or amendments.Opt-out/Contact Worcester County Food Bank:If you wish to opt-out of receiving future communications, please contact Worcester County Food Bank at the below address or phone number or submit your request via Worcester County Food Bank’s website Contact Us form.Postal Mail:Worcester County Food Bank474 Boston TurnpikeShrewsbury, MA 01545Telephone: (508) 842-3663All opt-out requests will be honored, but please be patient with us as it may take six (6) to eight (8) weeks for opt-out changes to be fully implemented.Should you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, contact Worcester County Food Bank at:Postal Mail:Attn: Communications DepartmentWorcester County Food Bank474 Boston TurnpikeShrewsbury, MA 01545  CONTACTWorcester County Food Bank 474 Boston Turnpike Shrewsbury, MA 01545T: 508 842 3663 F: 508 842 7405Administrative Hours Monday – Friday: 8am – 4:30pmWarehouse, Donation, Delivery and Agency Hours Monday – Friday: 8am – 3:30pmLINKSFind FoodVolunteerDonateSpeak UpLearn MoreContactPrivacy PolicySTAY CONNECTED© 2020 Worcester County Food Bank.
All Rights Reserved. Site Design.
Find FoodVolunteerDonateDonate FundsDonate FoodSpeak UpWhy AdvocateOur Advocacy PrioritiesOur Advocacy PartnersGet Involved in AdvocacySign Up for Action AlertsLearn MoreAboutOur PartnersTour WCFBStaff & BoardJobs & InternshipsCalendarNewsContactDONATE508-842-3663PARTNER AGENCY PORTALFind FoodVolunteerDonateDonate FundsDonate FoodSpeak UpWhy AdvocateOur Advocacy PrioritiesOur Advocacy PartnersGet Involved in AdvocacySign Up for Action AlertsLearn MoreAboutOur PartnersTour WCFBStaff & BoardJobs & InternshipsCalendarNewsContactDONATE
